<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EzyLearning: A Learning Platform By Sharing on KA Mansor</title>
    <link>https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EzyLearning: A Learning Platform By Sharing on KA Mansor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>STA104 - Introduction to Business Statistics</title>
      <link>https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/post/course2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/post/course2/</guid>
      <description>Course Learning Outcomes At the end of the course, students should be able to:
Explain the concept, the use and the application of basic statistical tools in descriptive and inferential statistics. (C2)
Determine appropriate statistical solution and interpreting the real world problem. (C5)
Propose the use of descriptive statistics in the area of computing. (A3)
Course Description This course introduces the basic statistical concepts in general applications. The topics include basic concepts of sampling methods, method of data collection, introductory methods in descriptive and inferential statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics with Business Applications MAT111</title>
      <link>https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/post/course1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/post/course1/</guid>
      <description>Course Information Course Learning Outcomes At the end of the course, students should be able to:
 Solve basic mathematical problems. ( C3 A1 P2 ) Apply mathematical concepts to solve mathematical problems in finance and banking. ( C4 A1 P2 ) Apply mathematical concepts to solve mathematical problems in trading and retailing. ( C5 P2 A1 )  Course Description The course is primarily designed to strengthen the fundamental concepts of mathematics with emphasis on business application and problem solving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ariff118.github.io/kamansor2/contact/</guid>
      <description>Kamarul Ariffin Mansor
Senior Lecturer
Faculty of Computer and Mathematical Sciences
UiTM Kedah Branch Campus
I’d love to hear from you, so feel free to reach out:
Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Kedah
Faculty of Computer and Mathematical Sciences
08400 Merbok
Kedah Darul Aman, MALAYSIA
ariff118@uitm.edu.my
Or connect with me on GitHub, Facebook, or Linkedin (links in top right).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>